Guide to the Professor William C. Moffit Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Teaching Materials
  - Misc. – Worksheets / Warm-ups Sketches (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Writing Guide (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - “Your University”, “March Your Way to Health” Article (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Finger Busters; "Basses Bassoons" (Ovs box 61, Folder 4)
  - Finger Busters; 1st Clarinet (Ovs box 61, Folder 5)
  - Finger Busters; C Flute (Ovs box 61, Folder 6)
  - Finger Busters; C Part (Ovs box 61, Folder 7)
- Research Sheet Music
  This series contains 3 boxes of sheet music used by William C. Moffit as research for his marching band arrangements. Music includes various classic children’s songs, traditional university songs, and the 1984 “Olympic Fanfare.” Material is arranged alphabetically. The sheet music ranges in date from 1944 to 1986, with the bulk of the dated material coming from the 1960s. Oversized sheet music may be found in OVS Box 61 and 62. Research materials used during Moffit's time at teh Jacksonville Community Band may be found in Series 17, Jacksonville Community Band Materials. Original folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible. Exceptions were made when folders were obviously misfiled or when no order was apparent.
  - “1812 Overture” (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - “A” Band Score (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - “A Brass Band” (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - “Aggie Fanfare” (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - “A Shot in the Dark” (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - “A Pretty Girl is Like a Melody” (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - “Abide with Me” (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Across the Field, September 4, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - “Adeste Fideles” (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - "All Through the Night” (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - “Aloha Oe” (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - “Amen” (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - “America” (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - “America the Beautiful” (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - “American Prelude” (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - “Angels Eyes”; Kai Winding Four Trombone Series (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - “Angels from the Realm of Glory” (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - “Another Opening, Another Show”, September 13, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - “Another Opening, Another Show”, November 29, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - “April in Paris Tag” (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - “Are You Sleeping?” (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - “Armed Forces Salute” (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - “Arthur’s Theme”; (Best That You Can Do) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - “Baby Tuba Walk”, August 23, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - “Bach with a Beat” (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - “Band Cheer No. 7” (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - “Battle Hymn” (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - “Battle Hymn of the Republic” (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - “Beautiful Dreamer” (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - “Begin the Beguine” (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - “Betty Co-Ed” (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - “Birth of the Blues” (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - “Birthday” (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - “Birthday Present” (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - “Black and Gold” (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - “Black Magic Woman” (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - “Blue Skies” (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - “Boogie Blues” (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - “Born Free” (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - “Braham’s Lullaby/Cradle Song” (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - “Brass for Christmas”; No. 3 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - “Bucket Fanfare”, November 16, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - “Bud Special”, November 27, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - “Bugle Calls Taps-Revelli-Chow” (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - “Bugler’s Dream” (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - “Bugler’s Dream II” (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - “Bugler’s Dream Olympic Fanfare” (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - “By the Light of the Silvery Moon”, August 1960 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - “Caissons” (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - “Calling Occupants of Interplanetary Craft” (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - “Camptown Cheer” (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - “Campus Chimes and Alma Mater” (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - “Can Can” (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - “Canadian Sunset” (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - “Can’t Take My Eyes Off You” (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - “Capriccio Italien”; Op. 30 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - “Charge On” (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - “Charleston” (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - “Chester” (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - “Chicago” (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - “Chorale America” (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - “Circus Extravaganza” (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - “Classical Cheers” (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - “Cohan Salute” (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - “College Songs” (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - “Collegiate” (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - “Comedian’s Gallop” (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - “Coming Up Roses”, December 1960 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - “Coming Up Rose”, November 28, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - “Crazy Rhythm” (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - “Dark Eyes” (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - “Deck the Halls” (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - “Deep River” (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - “Different Worlds” (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - “Dinah Score” Spiritual Pattern (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - “Discover America” (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - “Dixie” (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - “Dixie Bell Bailey” (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - “Do, Lord” (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - “Down By the Old Mill Stream” (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - “Doxology” (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - “El Relicario” (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - “Entry Fanfare” (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - “Entry of the Gladiators”; “Thunder and Blazes” (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - “Fanfare II” (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - “Fanfare ‘82” (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - “Fanfare”; Snare Drum, Tenor Drum, Bass Drum, Cymbal (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - “Farewell” (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - “Fascinating Rhythm” (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - “Festival Fanfare and March” (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - “Fight On”, September 1964 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - “Fight On” (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - “Fight Song Fanfare No. 3” (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - “Footnotes” (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - “From this Moment On” (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - “Funeral March” (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - “Games People Play” (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - “Girl Talk” (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - “Glow Worm” (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - “Goodnight Ladies” (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - “Grace Praeludium” (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - “Great Gate of Kiev” (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - “Gridiron Heroes” (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - “Hail, Hail” (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - “Hail the F.F.A” (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - “Hail to the Chief” (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - “Hambone” (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - “Hawaiian War Chant” (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - “Hearts and Flowers” (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - “Hello Dolly”, February 18, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - “Hello Indiana” (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - “Here Comes the Showboat” (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - “High Noon”; (Do Not Forsake Me) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - “Holy, Holy, Holy” (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - “Home, Sweet Home” (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - “Hook’s Theme” (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - “Hot Time” (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - “How Dry I Am” (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - “Howdy Do” (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - “I Love Paris” (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - “I Love Paris II” (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - “In the Good Old Summertime” (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - “It Had to Be You” (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - “It’s All Right with Me” (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - “It’s All Right with Me”; Kai Winding Eight Trombone Series (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - “Johnny’s Theme” (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - “Johnson Rag”, September 1960 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - “K-K-K –Katy” (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - “Life is a Song” (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - “Little Brown Tug” (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - “Lord Bless and Keep You” (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - “Louie, Louie” (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - “Lover”, October 1960 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - “Lover II”, October 12, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - “Love’s Old Sweet Song” (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - “Lullaby of Broadway” (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - “Mack the Knife”, December 1963 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - “Make Way” (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - “Malaguena” (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - “Mama-Papa “ Cheer (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - “March America” (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - “Marching Band Calisthenics” (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - “Marching Band Calisthenics” (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - “Marching Band Scoring Master Sheets” (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - “Margie” (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - “Marine’s Fanfare” (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - “Marine’s Hymn” (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - “Marine’s Hymn Bridge” (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - “Michigan”, October 22, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - “Michigan” (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - “Midnight Sun” (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - “Misty” (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Miscellaneous Music Transparencies (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - “Moffit’s Marching Warm-Up” (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - “Mombo Jombo” (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - “Mother” (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - “Mountain Greenery”, September 1963 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - “Muskrat Ramble” Combo Score (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - “Music for a Festival” (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - “Music for a Festival” for a Military Band (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Musical Highlights from “Rocky” (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - “My Friends Could See Me Now” (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - “Navy Hymn” (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - “Navy Log March” (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - “New York” (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - “New York, New York” (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - “Night and Day” (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - “No, No 1,000 Times No!” (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - “Not Fragile”, January 1976 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - “Now the Day is Over” (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - “O’ Columbia” (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - “O’ Columbia the Gem” (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - “O’ Tannenbaum” (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - “Oh, Mr. Moon” (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - “Ohio, the Heart of It All” (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - “Old MacDonald Had a Farm” (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - “Olympic Fanfare”, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - “On the Banks” Intro (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - “On the Banks of the Wabash” (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - “Onward Christian Soldiers” (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - “Our Boys Will Shine” (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - “Over the River” (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - “Over the Waves” (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - “Oye Negra”, December 12, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - “Part I” (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - “Patriot Intros” (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - “Patterns for Percussion”; Volume II, Excerpt 1 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - “Peanut Vendor", May 1963 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - “Pennsylvania Polka” (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - “Pink Panther” (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - “Pitt Victory Song” (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - “Powerhouse Drums” (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - “Prayer of Thanksgiving” (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - “Pre-Game Fight Song” (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - “Raindrops Keep Falling on My Head” (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - “Red River Valley” (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - “Regards” (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - “Reveille” (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - “Rhythm of Life” (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - “Rock a bye Baby” (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - “Ruffles and Flourishes” (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - “Salute to the Olympians” (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - “San Francisco” (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - “Sain II”, October 1963 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - “Say It With Music” (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - “Say Yes Fanfare” (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - “Say Yes to Michigan” (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - “School Days” (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - “Silly Love Songs”, February 12, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - “Silvery Moon” (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - “Sing a Cougar Song” (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - “Sheet Music “1” (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - “#25” (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - “1st T-Bone” (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - “Showcase For Band” (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - “Slaughter on Tenth Avenue”, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - “Something for Cat II” (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - “Someone’s in the Kitchen” (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - “Song of the Vagabonds” (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - “Sound of Music” (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - “South Rampart Street Parade” (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - “Spook Music” (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - “Stardust”, October 1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - “Stars and Stripes Forever” (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - “Star Spangled Banner”, August 7, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - “Star Spangled Banner”, August 1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - “Star Spangled Banner” (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - “St. Elmo’s Fire” (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - “Strauss Odyssey”, October 25, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - “Spott’s Hail”, October 14, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - “Swanee”; composer: Gershwin (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - “Swanee”; composer; Gates, Jerry (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - “Sweet Adeline” (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - “Tailgate Ramble” (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - “Tannenbaum” (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - “TAPS”, May 18, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - “Tea for Two” (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - “Temptation”, February 9, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - “That’s My Baby” (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - “The Bells of St. Mary’s” (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - “The Care and Feeding of the Band Musician No. 1” (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - “The Care and Feeding of the Band Musician”; Middle School Calisthenics (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - “The Farmer in the Dell” (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - “The Greatest Show on Earth” (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - “The More We Get Together” (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - “The Purdue Hymn” (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - “The Trolley Song” (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - "There Will Never Be Another You”; Kai Winding Four Trombone Series” (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - “Three Blind Mice”, March 20, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - “Three Days” (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - “Three Intradas for Brass Choir” (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - “Tiger Rag” (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - “TRUE Pals Fight Song” (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - “Tuba Christmas Scores” (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Tuba Christmas Show Preparation (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - “Tuba Hail” (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - “Tuba Instrument Listings” (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - “Tu-ba or Not Tu-ba” (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Tuba Patriots Information (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - “Tuba Taps” (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - “Twinkle-Twinkle” (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Untitled Sheet Music (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Untitled Sheet Music (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Untitled Sheet Music (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Untitled Sheet Music (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - “Vaudeville Ending” (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - “Wabash Cannonball” (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - "Wait ‘Til the Sun Shines Nellie” (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - “Wake Up Serenade” (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - “Wander Indiana Festival Version” (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - “Wander Indiana”; Lewis, Huey (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - “Wander Indiana” Slide Show (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - “Well Get It” (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - “What, More Fanfares!” (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - “What’s the Matter Give a Cheer” (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - “Wheaties” (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - “When Johnny Comes Marching Home”, May 8, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - “When Johnny Comes Marching Home” (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - “When Yuba Plays the Rumba on the Tuba” (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - “Work Song” March (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - “Yellow Rose of Texas” (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - “Yellow Submarine” (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - “You’re a Grand Old Flag” (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - “Zing! Went the Stings of My Heart”, August 1960 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - “Zing II”; “Zing Went the Strings of My Heart” (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - "I'm Thrilled" (Ovs box 61, Folder 8)
- University Fight Songs
  This series contains 9 folders of various university fight songs. It was Bill Moffit’s custom for his band to play rival schools’ fight songs as a show of respect and good sportsmanship. Included are songs from 10 different universities. Material is arranged alphabetically. Original folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible. Exceptions were made when folders were obviously misfiled or when no order was apparent.
  - “Adelita” (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - “ASU Fight Song”; Arkansas State University (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - “Big Red”; Lamar University (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - “Bull Dog March Medley ‘92” (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - “Fight Song”; Louisiana Tech University (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - “Jaguar Pride”; University of South Alabama Fight Song (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - “Let’s Here it for Uno”; University of New Orleans Fight Song (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - University of Colorado; Cornell University; University of Florida (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - USL Fight Song (Box 7, Folder 79)
- Moffit Arrangements of SWC Schools Fight Songs
  This series contains 11 folders of Moffit arrangements for various university fight songs. The universities included in this series are all Southwest Conference affiliates. It was Bill Moffit’s custom for his band to play rival schools’ fight songs as a show of respect and good sportsmanship. Material is organized alphabetically. Original folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible. Exceptions were made when folders were obviously misfiled or when no order was apparent.
  - “Aggie War Hymn”; Texas A&M (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - “Baylor Fight Song”, September 22, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - “Baylor Fite Song”, August 23, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - “Baylor III Fight Song”, October 4, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - “Circus Entry” (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - “Fight Raiders”; Texas Tech, November 17, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Perunas; SMU (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - “Rice Fight Song”, August 14, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - “Rice Fight Song II" (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - "TCU March" (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - "Texas Fite”, October 31, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 90)
- Manuscript Parts
  This series contains 4 boxes of manuscript parts sheet music for a marching band. Material is arranged alphabetically. Additional manuscripts parts from Moffit's time at the Jacksonville Community Band many be found in Series 17, Jacksonville Community Band Materials. Original folder and item order has been maintained whenever possible. Exceptions were made when folders were obviously misfiled or when no order was apparent.
  - "4 H Plowing Song" (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "76 T-Bones" (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "'1812' 'A' Band, Page 1," "'1812' 'A' Band, Page 2," "'1812' 'B' Band" (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - "A Lot of Livin’ to Do,” “A Lot of Livin’ to Do II” (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - "A Shot in the Dark" (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "A Quiet Gass II," "A Quiet Gass II" (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "Across the Field" (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - "Action Fanfare #1" (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - "Action Fanfare #3" (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - "Aggie Fanfare" (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - "Aggie War Hymn – Texas A&M” (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - "Ain't No Woman" (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "Ajax – Colgate” (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - "Alexander's Ragtime Band" (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - "All I Ever Need is You" (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - "Alley Cat" (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - "Alma Mater" (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - "Alma Mater Chimes II" (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - "Alma Mater – Hail to Thee” (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - "Alouette" (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - "Also Sprach Zarathustra and Capriccio Italien Op. 45” (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - "Always True to You" (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - "America" (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - "America the Beautiful,” “America the Beautiful II,” “America the Beautiful III,” “America the Beautiful 4” (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - "Angels from the Realm of Glory" (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - "Angels We Have Heard" (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - "Another Opening," "Another Opening III" (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - "April in Paris" (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - "Arizona State" (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - "Armed Forces Medley" (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - "Auld Lang Syne Choral,” “Auld Lang Syne Choral,” “Auld Lang Syne II 'March,'” “Auld Lang Syne – Farewell,” “Auld Lang Syne March” (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - "Away in a Manger" (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - "Bach with a Beat," "Bach with a Beat II" (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - "Band Cheers," "Band Cheers I" (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - "Band Cheers #1-#2" (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - "Band Cheers #3-#4" (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - "Band Cheers #5-#6" (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - "Band Cheers #7-#8" (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - "Band Day Buffet," "Band Day Buffet II" (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - "Band Intros" (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - "Basin St. Blues I," "Basin St. Blues II" (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - "'Bass' Clarinet Polka II" (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - "Bass Skit" (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - "Battle Hymn" (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - "Baubles, Bangles and Beads II" (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - "Baylor Fight" (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - "Beer Barrel Polka" (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - "Begin the Beguine," "Begin the Beuine March" (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - "Big Noise from Winnetka" (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - "Big Spender" (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - "Big Ten Medley P.1," "Big Ten Medley P.2" (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - "Bilbao Song" (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - "Bill Bailey’s Combo,” “Bill Bailey’s Combo – Do Not Run” (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - "Bittersweet Samba" (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - "B.J. and the Bear" (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - "Black Bottom" (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - "Black Magic" (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - "Blues in the Night" (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - "Boatman Cheer" (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - "Boogie Blues" (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - "Born Free" (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - "Brazil" (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - "Buck Dance II" (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - "Bud – Rudolph” (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - "Budweiser" (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - "Bugle Calls" (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - "But Not for Me" (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - "Caissons Song (N. Carolina State)” (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - "Calliope" (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - "Car Wash" (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - "Carioca" (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - "California Dreaming I,” “California Dreaming II” (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - "California Fight Song" (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - "Calling Occupants" (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - "Can Can" (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - "Car Hop" (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - "Car Themes – Olds, Cheve, Ford” (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - "Cardinal Fite" (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - "Carolina Victory (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - "Cecilia" (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - "Centennery" (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - "Change Music," "Super Suds" (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - "Charleston" (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - "Cheers II" (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - "Chester" (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - "Chrysalis" (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - "Clean Sweep" (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - "Clapping Song Cheer – Volga Boat Cheer” (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - "Clarinet Range Builders" (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - "Clark Gum Shuffle" (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - "Cohan Salute Page 1,” “Cohan Salute Page 2” (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - "Colonel Bogey" (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - "Comedian’s Galop,” “Comedian’s Galup - 2” (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - "Concert Opener" (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - "Cotton Eyed Joe" (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - "Cougar Intros" (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - "Cougar Power" (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - "Cougar Showcase A-Band, Page 1" (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - "Cougar Showcase B-Band, Page 2" (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - "Crazy Rhythm" (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - "Dancing in the Dark" (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - "Deck the Halls" (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - "Deer Park Alma Mater" (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - "Different Worlds II" (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - "Do Lord," "Do Lord II" (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - "Donkey Serenade" (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - "Don't Fence Me In" (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - "Don't Let the Sun Go Down on Me II" (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - "Double Mint Gum" (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - "Down, Down the Field," Syracuse University (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - "Dream" (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - "Dreamville" (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - "Dragnet" (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - "'Duel' Conductor 'A,' All Drum Parts Here – Page 1,” “'Duel' Conductor 'A' – Page 2,” “'Duel' Conductor 'B' – Page 1,” “'Duel' Conductor 'B' – Page 2” (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - "El Cumbanchero" (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - "Eli's Comin'" (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - "Evlis Page 1," "Elvis Page 2" (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - "En Kelohenu" (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - "Espańa Cani P.1,” "Espańa Cani P.2” (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - "Evergreen" (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - "Ezekiel" (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "Extra Cheers" (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "Fanfare #1 - #2" (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - "Fanfare #1- #2, Brass” (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - "Fanfare #4 - #5 - #6” (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - "Fanfare #4” (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - "Fanfare #5" (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - "Fanfare #7 (MSU Fight Song) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - "Favorite Hymns, Set 4” (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - "Feelin’ Groovy” (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - "'Festival' Fanfare" (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - "Festival March (From 'Music for a Festival')” (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - "Fever," "Fever II" (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - "Fight On,” “Fight On II” (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - "Fight Raiders" (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - "Fight Song Endings in A♭,E♭,B♭” (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - "Fight Song Ending – 63” (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - "Fight Song Ending – T. Hegerberg” (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - "Fight Song Fanfare,” “Fight Song Fanfare #3” (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - "Fight Song – MSU” (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - "Fight Song II – MSU" (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - "Fight Song Tag – Hegerberg” (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - "Fight Song – UH” (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - "The First Noel” (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - "Five Foot Two” (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - "Five Days from Home” (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - "Forward Falcons" (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - "4 Leaf Clover" (Box 9, Folder 30)